<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <template id="s_customer_care" name="customer care">
        <section class="s_customer_care pb24" style="min-height: 800px;">
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-md-2">
                        <ul class="list-unstyled list_side_bar o_editable ml-5">
                            <li class="selected_li_sidebare">Customer Care</li>
                            <li>Terms</li>
                            <li>Contact Us</li>

                        </ul>
                    </div>
                    <div class="col-md-10 p-0 o_editable">
                        <div class="row p-0 justify-content-center">


                            <div class="col-md-6 p-5 pt80 s_about_us_text_4 o_editable">
                                <span>
                                    Shipping
                                    Bliss Flower Boutique is delighted to offer shipping of fresh flowers and gifts with
                                    free same day delivery within the UAE - Dubai, Abu Dhabi, Ras Al Khaimah, Sharjah,
                                    Ajman and Umm Al Quwain for orders over 300 AED.

                                    We have three delivery slots per day; 8am-12pm, 12pm-5pm and 5-10pm.

                                    The cut off time for each delivery slot is 2 hours prior to the slot - please note
                                    due to high demand and capacity occasionally from time to time some slots maybe
                                    unavailable.

                                    We offer free delivery to all emirates for all orders over 300 AED.

                                    For orders under 300 AED, a 50AED surcharge will be added on checkout to the
                                    following areas.


                                    Fujairah:
                                    Including Kalba, Khorfakkan, Dibba and Masafi

                                    Sharjah:
                                    Falaj, Maleha and Al Madam

                                    Dubai:
                                    Hatta

                                    Umm Al Quwain Remote:
                                    Al Mualla

                                    Abu Dhabi Remote:
                                    Al Yarya, Bateen Liwa, Asab, Sabkah, Jereirah, Taraq, Arada, Zayed City, Habshan,
                                    Ghiyathi, Al Ruwais and Al Mirfa
                                </span>
                            </div>

                            <div class="col-md-6 p-5 pt80 s_about_us_text_4 o_editable">
                                <span class="o_editable" >
                                    Changes and Cancellations

                                    If you change your mind, or wish to cancel your order, please contact us the soonest
                                    via info@Blissuae.com

                                    Provided your order has not been taken into production we will be able to change
                                    your order or cancel the order and provide a refund where applicable.

                                    If the order is out for delivery, but has not reached its destination we will aim to
                                    contact the driver to cancel the delivery. However we will not be able to provide a
                                    refund of the product due to the vulnerability and quality of the fresh products
                                    used.

                                    Refund Policy

                                    In the unlikely event you are unhappy with your purchase at Bliss, Bliss FZCO may
                                    depending on the circumstances, refund the price of the product or provide an other
                                    solutions such as resending the product or resending a different gift of the same
                                    value.

                                    As we are working with fresh products it will be to our complete discretion what
                                    solution will be suitable and applicable.

                                    When a replacement or other solution is granted we aim to have this resolved within
                                    1 working day. When a refund is provided please allow 7-10 days depending on your
                                    bank for it to reach your account

                                    Customer Care

                                    Have any questions, comments or concerns?
                                    Please feel free to contact us at info@blissuae.com

                                </span>
                            </div>
                        </div>

                    </div>

                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
    </template>


</odoo>